All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm going to be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Horty Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict.
About time you showed up, Straw Hat! I can't believe you came!
Wait, Luffy, what did you call me? Huh?
Just now, it was almost my name, but...
Yeah, I was wrong about you. You're a wuss, but more than just a crybaby. So I'll call you Weepy Hoshi. It's an upgrade!
Oh yes, you pirates. We'll bow! The same as everybody else. Just you, wait.
You see? These humans are more than capable of holding their own, yet they kneel before me.
That's right. In a moment you'll be just like them, Straw Hats. I'll be King of the Fishmen, King of the Humans, and King of the Pirates!
Is that so?
We have a hundred thousand men!
Hey, Luffy!
Those four million berries are mine!
No, they're mine!
It's too easy!
Kill him!
What the hell just happened?!
But he didn't do anything, and he still knocked them all out!
Your name's Hordy, right? I'm about to kick your ass.
You want to become the king of a country or whatever? Fine, I don't care.
King of the Pirates? Nuh-uh. That's my job.
Deadly attacks, one after another! Zoro and Sanji join the battle!
King of the Pirates?
All that in one shot!
I've never seen power like that!
So that's him. That's Straw Hat Luffy!
That's Luffy!
He's gonna mop the floor with us for sure!
Where do you think you're going?
If you won't stand with your people on the day of our uprising,
I might as well kill you myself.
It's true.
We may have lost 50,000.
But take heart.
We still have 50,000 left!
Those insufferable straw hat pirates have sought to shadow our dreams at every turn.
They must pay!
The traitor Jinbei is no better!
He follows in Otohime's footsteps and befriends the humans!
But that is not the future we fishmen wish to create!
He's right!
Straw hat's a damn human!
What the hell does he know about our people?
And Jinbei!
If he wants to turn his back on his brothers, kill him too!
No!
Geez!
You knocked out too many!
Leave some for me!
Oh yeah!
My bad!
Hey!
Don't get ahead of yourself!
Huh?
I'm taking 30,000!
Got it?
Lost head?
Shut up!
Dirty cook!
Oh!
It looks like we've got a full house tonight!
Okay!
Thankfully I've got just the jam to start this battle off right!
Ow!
Yaaayoo!
I'm not sure, Brooke.
I don't think they came here to see you.
Oh ho ho ho ho!
Robin's cool as always!
Or just cold!
No way!
They didn't even listen to your speech!
Because I used my inside voice again!
Huh?
He's got way too much pride to admit it!
Oh!
Kill them!
You're dead now!
Don't mess with us!
Okay!
Go Third Gear!
Just come at me!
I'll take all of you!
Come, come!
His arm is...
I know! It's huge!
Here goes! Show pistol!
Quick, we had better assist him.
Damn, Luffy. Wait for us.
I have to help.
I can't bear to see tears in those eyes.
Single-handedly, you are a defender.
Protecting the virtues of others day after day.
But today, we're here.
We'll protect them for you.
If I can't wipe the tears from a pretty girl's eyes,
I'm no man at all.
Let me go and teach him a thing or two.
After this, we can celebrate over drinks at the Mermaid Cafe.
What do you say?
Stop yapping and fight!
Oh, yay! Show!
This is heaven for me.
I won't let you destroy it.
You still don't want to give up?
Well, more fun for me.
One hundred and eight!
Calibre Phoenix!
What are you looking at? Let's fight!
I was thinking.
This island is teeming with invaluable archeological resources.
The way you're rampaging around and damaging it.
You ought to be ashamed.
The people...
They're all treasures!
Trianta, look!
What's happening?
And clutch.
Look!
What's happened?
And clutch!
Look at that crown!
They're ready to rock!
Ow!
Everybody say,
Woo!
You've all been a lovely audience today!
Got you now, little guy!
Kung fu point!
Whoa! He got bigger!
I'll take you all on, bring it!
Dude, what kind of raccoon are you?
Oh, that is the last straw!
Special attack, Green Star Devil!
Huh?
Help me!
Hey!
Take this!
And this!
And this too!
Had enough?
They call me the Pup Green Master!
I'm the all-powerful Loose Supper!
Stop it!
Hey, nice timing, Nami!
And here I thought you'd gotten stronger over those two years.
Guess I was wrong.
This fight's starting to get super exciting now, huh?
I'd say a 50,000 man brawl is the perfect time to take them for a test drive!
Test drive?
Did you say them?
Them who?
The Sunny just got two brand new weapons!
Big ones!
Do you guys wanna see them?
Yeah!
Of course we do!
Wow!
Super!
What?
I gotta know!
You think we'll be safer on this ship than out here?
See for yourself!
However badass you think it's gonna be, it's ten times better than that!
You're all... so strong!
I don't believe this!
You sorry wimps didn't even put up a fight!
You should keep an eye on your princess!
That's a pretty big target!
She's mine now!
What a shot!
They didn't need me after all!
What happened?
Back to the
edge on a Road to the
Channel.
Post-like.
Ha, Ha, Ha!
Did you see that crap?
He deflected Captain Horny's water charm with his own like it was nothing at all!
I am so done with that big blue trade-off. He's as much trouble as Straw Hats. Maybe more!
Huh. That raw power of yours is harnessed very poorly.
Your Fishman Karate needs work.
Wait a minute. I've heard stories about this guy. He was the first Fishman to join the Seven Warlords.
Yeah, and then after he resigned, his bounty jumped up to 400 million berries, right?
This is hopeless. We can't win against that guy.
Why don't you fools stop chattering and start fighting?
If you intend to kill the princess, you'll have to square with the rest of us first.
Well, what are you waiting for?
There is nothing left for you lot but to go forth and fight!
You've gotta be kidding!
This is boring.
Such impertinence.
I would advise you to hold your tongue for the time being.
At least, until you've broken through our defenses!
Hope you're not attached to that sword! I'll smash it to bits!
Go forth! Iron Shell Squad!
Go forth!
Please!
Will you train me as a swordsman?
Stop being Hawkeye! Right down to that oversized sword!
We're nothing but weaklings! I'm wasting my damn time with this!
Damn it! How many times is this gonna happen to me? I said it was gonna get stronger, didn't I?
I swear, I swear, I'm never going to lose again!
I swear, I'm never going to lose again!
Three sword style!
Black rope!
Tatsuma!
Tso!
Ah!
He cut through their shells!
Tso!
Ah! He cut through their shells! It's like they were made out of cheese!
What the hell? They all drop like flies! Is this guy the Crim Reaper or what?
It's not Uber!
This is sick!
It's a sort of hurricane!
Ryan, you're gonna get cut!
How long is this thing gonna last?
Until you get to hell!
Why don't you idiots use your brains?
Inflate your bubbles! Let's go!
Attack from the sky! Kill Princess Shirahoshi!
So it's like that.
Move it!
Watch out! We'll stab you!
Go, Harusamban!
It's the Sea Urchin Spike Unit!
And their leader Harusamban!
Before you do anything else, take out the kicking guy!
Harusamban!
Well, what are you gonna do now, huh?
Sanji! Do be careful!
How can you be so calm at a time like this?
Hey!
It's been a while since then.
Sanji!
I ran like hell.
Come back, Candy Boy!
Over my dead body!
I brought my favorite dress just for you!
Why don't you try it on?
Don't be shy! It's just us!
That's not the problem!
Forget it!
Through the rain...
And the snow...
Through thunder and lightning...
I never stopped...
Say your prayers!
You stubborn bastard!
Aren't you adorable?
You can't just run away from us forever, you know!
One of these days was certain to catch right up to you!
Oh, Sanji!
I've gotten myself out of tougher spots than this, haven't I?
Sanji!
Damn you!
Can't win! Don't fight!
Did I already forget everything that happened back at Sabahodi?
Sanji!
I need those recipes if I want to get stronger!
And taking them down is the only way!
Bring it on!
Candy boy!
There's no escape, Sanji!
You're all mine!
Goodness gracious!
Now you're all surrounded, aren't you?
Sanji!
Sanji darling!
Sweet my sugar bear!
My courage had left me, and there was nowhere to run.
Then...
What the...
He's gone!
Huh?
I found a new path.
Don't you wait!
And then...
Before long...
I was flying.
You're flying!
Huh?
Haha!
Skywalk!
Awesome!
Sanji can walk on air now!
Like those other guys!
Skywalk.
Oh, I see.
Not moonwalk.
Hey scumbags!
Whoa!
He's flying!
If you've got something to say to the princess,
you'll have to go through me first!
Uh...
Cause I just happen to be her.
Knight in shining armor!
Thank you, Sanji!
Are you some kind of wise guy?
Let's cook these small fries!
Diablo!
The Jomber!
The Wall of Fear!
Spector!
Hey Hordy!
It's almost over.
So you can just sit tight.
You can send a hundred thousand or ten million guys after us!
But every single one of them is going down!
You hear me?
Brooke and Robin tear through the battlefield with their new skills,
forcing the new Fishman pirates to counter-attack with their deadly Venom squad.
Not to be outdone, Frankie shows off a new weapon of monumental proportions.
His crewmates are dazzled, but Hordy may have something even more impressive in store.
On the next, One Piece!
Unveiled!
The Secret Weapons of the Sunny!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!